https://www.cityholding.com/privacy

Skip to main content
Our branch lobbies are now open!                                Our branch lobbies are now open!                                Our branch lobbies are now open!                    Our branch lobbies are now open!
Home
Locations
About
Contact
Investors
Careers
Toggle navigation
Personal
CheckingSavings & CDsDebit CardsCredit CardsVideo BankerAvoiding OverdraftsAvoiding Overdrafts
What's Right for Me?How Can I Avoid Overdrafts?Manage My Overdraft CoverageWhat City Does to Help
Security Resources
Business
CheckingLoansCredit CardsCash ManagementOnline Business BankingCommercial Lenders
Mortgage & Loans
MortgagesMortgages
Buy or RefinanceFirst Time HomebuyerBuilding Your Dream HomeBuy Now, Build LaterPhysicians Mortgage Program
Home Equity Lines of CreditPersonal LoansAuto LoansCommercial LoansOriginators
Wealth Management
ServicesOfficers
Online & Mobile Banking
Online BankingMobile BankingMobile Banking
Mobile DepositText BankingZelle FAQsMobile App FAQs
Bill PayeStatementsDigital WalletMobile App Demos
Privacy Policy
About Us
Rev 2/10
What does City National Bank do with your personal information?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income
account balances and payment history
credit history and credit card or other debt
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons City National Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Does City National Bank share? Yes
Can you limit this sharing? No
For our marketing purposes—to offer our products and services to you
Does City National Bank share? Yes
Can you limit this sharing? No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Does City National Bank share? Yes
Can you limit this sharing? No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your transactions and experiences
Does City National Bank share? Yes
Can you limit this sharing? No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
Does City National Bank share? No
Can you limit this sharing? We don't share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
Does City National Bank share? No
Can you limit this sharing? We don't share
Questions? Call or visit your local branch.
What we do
How does City National Bank protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does City National Bank collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or deposit money
apply for insurance or
apply for a loan
use your credit or debit card
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Our affiliates include financial companies such as property service companies and insurance agents
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
City National Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include advertising agencies and service providers
Information we get from you when visiting our website.
“We use cookies and similar technologies to identify your browser or device. Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies do not contain any data that enables us to determine your actual identity, and they are useful because they allow a website to recognize a user’s device. You can find more information about cookies at: http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
Cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently and remembering your preferences, and generally improve the user experience. They can also help to ensure that advertisements you see online are more relevant to you and your interests.
Pixel tags are small, invisible images on a webpage or other document that allow us to set, read and modify cookies. When you visit a website, the pixel tag helps us better understand how you interact with our website by observing which pages you visited.
We use analytics tools and other third party technologies to collect non-personal information in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use our site or online services. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, features use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and other similar information.
The third party analytics companies who collect information on the Site and/or other online products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.
Opting out and your privacy rights
To learn more about or opt-out of interest-based advertising, please visit the industry opt-out pages operated by the Network Advertising Initiative and by the Digital Advertising Alliance. To obtain more information and/or to opt-out of personalized advertising for Google and its partners sites, use the following link: http://adssettings.google.com. Please note, even if you opt-out of interest based advertising, you may still see other kinds of non-interest based advertising from us.
Company
About
Locations
Contact
Investors
Careers
Accessibility
Community Investment
